# PRASAD

## Digital Marketing / SEO Analyst

## My Contact

prasadprasad293@gmail.com

**(** +91 8754204775

43, Veeriyampalayam, Coimbatore, Tamil Nadu, India

### **Hard Skill**

- · Keyword research
- On-page optimization
- Technical SEO
- Algorithmic updates
- · Link building

#### **Soft Skill**

- Observation
- Decision making
- Communication
- Multi-tasking

## **Education Background**

- Tamil Nadu College of Engineering BE in Mechanical Engineering Completed in 2018
- Government Polytechnic College Diploma in Production Engineering

Completed in 2015

Padmavathi Ammal High School SSLC

Completed in 2012

#### **About Me**

As an SEO analyst with 2 years of experience. I specialize in analyzing and optimizing websites in order to improve their search engine rankings and increase organic traffic. This involves conducting keyword research to identify relevant terms and phrases that people are searching for, and then implementing strategies to optimize websites and content for those keywords.

## **Professional Experience**

#### Onroadz | SEO Analyst

Feb 2022 - Jan 2023 [present notice period 1 month] **Key responsibilities:** 

- · Conducting keyword research to identify relevant terms and phrases that people are searching for.
- Analyzing websites to identify technical issues and areas for optimization, such as broken links, duplicate content, and crawl
- Building and maintaining high-quality backlinks to a website in order to improve its search engine rankings.
- · Analyzing website metrics and data, such as traffic and conversion rates, to understand how users are interacting with a

#### Webnox Technologies | SEO Analyst

Jan 2021 - Jan 2022

#### **Key responsibilities:**

- · Developing and implementing SEO strategies that align with a client's business goals.
- · Staying up-to-date on the latest trends and best practices in SEO and adapting strategies as necessary.
- A/B testing and analyzing the results of various SEO tactics.
- · Working with web developers to implement SEO strategies.
- Analyzing and reporting on website traffic and keyword performance.

#### **Achievements**

2022 - 2023Ranked Onroadz Car Rental and Bike Rental pages in the First page of Google

Ranked websites from Other countries like 2021 - 2022Australia, and New Zealand on the first page of SERP